(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
本日はホロライブ5thジェネレーションライブ、
「Twinkle 4 You」にご来場いただきありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming today to Hololive 5th
Generation Live, "Twinkle 4 You."
ねぽらぼの「ぽ」！尾丸ポルカでーす！
The "Po" of NePoLaBo! I'm Omaru Polka!
みんなおるか〜？
Is everyone here?
おーるぜー！ポルカもおるか〜？
We're here! Polka, are you here too?
おるよー！
I'm here!
そして、えらーいライオン！
ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんです。
And, the good lion!
Hololive 5th Gen, I'm Shishiro Botan.
ライブを最後まで楽しんでいただくために、
皆様へいくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live show to the end,
we have a few announcements to make.
はい！まずはじめに、会場の皆様へご案内です。
Yes! First, an announcement for those at the venue.
本公演は、声を出しての応援が可能です！
Cheering out loud is permitted for this performance!
ただし、周りのお席の人に迷惑となるような
However, please do not shout in a way that
大声を出す行為はしないように、ご協力をお願いいたします。
disturbs those around you. We appreciate your cooperation.
また、立ち上がっての応援も大歓迎です！
Also, cheering while standing is more than welcome!
ただし、モッシュ、ダイブ、ジャンプ等の危険行為は
禁止とさせていただきます。
However, dangerous acts like moshing, diving,
or jumping are prohibited.
ペンライトも、大きく振り回して周りの人の視界を遮ったり、
Please also be careful not to obstruct the view of others
ぶつかったりしないように、ご注意ください。
or hit them by swinging your penlights excessively.
また、指定の席からのご移動はしないよう、お願いいたします。
Also, please refrain from moving from your assigned seat.
周囲のお客様に配慮した上で、思いっきり盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get excited to our heart's content while being
considerate of those around us!
本公演は、避難誘導等の消灯を行ないます。
During this show, lights will be turned off for
evacuation guidance purposes.
万が一、避難が必要になった場合は、
In the unlikely event that an evacuation
すぐに非常灯を点灯しますので、係員の指示に従って
いただきますよう、お願いします。
becomes necessary, emergency lights will turn on.
Please follow the staff's instructions.
公演終了後は、規制退場を行います。
After the show, there will be a regulated exit.
スタッフの指示があるまで、ご自分の席でお待ちください。
Please wait in your seat until instructed by the staff.
また、イベント中、気分が悪くなったり、
Also, if you feel unwell during the event,
何かあった場合は、早めに近くのスタッフにお知らせください。
or if anything happens, please notify a nearby
staff member immediately.
場内での許可のない録音、撮影は禁止となっております。
Unauthorized recording or photography inside the
venue is strictly prohibited.
そのような行為を見つけた場合は、ご退場いただく場合がございます。
If such acts are discovered, you may be asked to leave.
携帯電話やスマートフォンは、音や振動を止めて、
Please turn off the sound and vibration on your
見えないところにしまっておいてください。
mobile phones and keep them out of sight.
そして本公演は、映像配信、及び写真撮影用のカメラが
Furthermore, for this performance, cameras for
会場内に入るため、お客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
streaming and photography will be present, and the
audience may be captured in the footage.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションや今後の活動に
Please note that these images and videos may be
使用する可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
used for promotion and future activities.
危険行為や禁止行為を見つけた場合、
スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございます。
If dangerous or prohibited acts are observed, the
staff may issue a warning.
ルールを守っていただけない場合には、安全確保のため、
If the rules are not followed, for the sake of safety,
公演を一時中断、もしくは中止となる可能性もございます。
the show may be suspended or cancelled.
ルールをしっかり守って、みんなで楽しいライブにしましょう！
Let's follow the rules strictly and make this a
fun live performance for everyone!
続いて...
Next...
配信でご覧の皆様への注意事項をお伝えします。
we will share some precautions for those watching via the live stream.
最善の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、
We are taking every possible preparation for this live stream,
生配信の特性上、
but due to the nature of live broadcasting,
不慮の障害で映像の乱れや一時停止などが起こる可能性があります。
unexpected issues like video distortion or pauses may occur.
あらかじめこちらはご了承下さいませ。
Please understand this in advance.
そして、本ライブの録音、録画、
Furthermore, the recording of audio and video,
ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りしています。
mirror streaming, and illegal uploading of this performance are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して
Instead, we highly welcome you
画像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは大歓迎です。
to take screenshots and post them on social media.
本公演のハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ「ねぽらぼT4U」です。
The hashtag for this performance is #NepolaboT4U.
ぜひハッシュタグを使ってライブを一緒に盛り上げてください。
Please use the hashtag and let's get hyped for the live show together!
以上が開演前のご案内となります。
That concludes the pre-show announcement.
ライブの開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a little longer until the show begins.
一緒に盛り上がって楽しんでいきましょう。
Let's all get excited and have a great time!
一緒に盛り上がっていこう！
Let's get hyped together!
みんなのこと見てるからな！
I'll be watching all of you!
推しの曲...
My favorite's song...
めっちゃいいね！
is so good!
みるハコ...
Miru Hako...
...チャーンス！
...Chance!
みるハコなら、臨場感たっぷりで推しのコンテンツが楽しめる。
With Miru Hako, you can enjoy your favorite's content with full immersion.
みるハコ最高！
Miru Hako is the best!
推し事増やそう！
Let's do more fan activities!
みるハコ！
Miru Hako!
配信中。
Now streaming.
開演までいましばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while until the start of the show.
携帯電話は電源を切るかマナーモードに設定してください
Please turn off your cell phone or set it to silent mode.
撮影・録音・録画は禁止とさせていただきます
Photography, audio recording, and video recording are prohibited.
公演終了後は規制退場を行います。
After the performance, there will be restricted/guided exit.
グッズラインナップ
Goods Lineup
hololive 5th Generation Live 「Twinkle 4 You」 ねぽらぼ
hololive 5th Generation Live "Twinkle 4 You" Nepolabo
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a while for the show to start.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all guests in attendance.
公演終了後は 規制退場を行います。
A regulated exit will be conducted after the show.
グッズラインナップ
Goods Lineup
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ！
Weiss Schwarz!
ホロライブプロダクションが...
Hololive Production is...
...またまたカードに大集合！
...gathering once more on cards!
広がるヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiss Schwarz expands.
ブースターパック ホロライブプロダクション Vol.2 好評発売中
Booster Pack Hololive Production Vol. 2, now on sale!
ブシロード
Bushiroad.
推しの曲、めっちゃいいね！
My favorite's song is so good!
みるハコ！
Miruhako!
みるハコなら臨場感たっぷりで、推しのコンテンツが楽しめる
With Miruhako, you can enjoy your favorite's content with plenty of presence.
みるハコ最高！
Miruhako is the best!
音と映像体験、みるハコ
Sound and video experience, Miruhako.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin shortly. Please wait.
ホロライブ 5th Generation Live Twinkle 4 You に
Thank you for coming to
ご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Hololive 5th Generation Live "Twinkle 4 You."
今夜はホロライブ5期生、オレンジ担当、
Tonight, I'm hololive 5th Gen, in charge of orange,
みんなの心のエナジードリンク、桃鈴ねねです！
everyone's heart's energy drink, Momosuzu Nene!
皆さん、こんらみー！
Everyone, Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです。
I'm hololive 5th Gen's Yukihana Lamy.
ライブを最後まで楽しんでいただくために、
To help everyone enjoy the live to the end,
皆様へいくつかご案内させていただきます。
we have a few announcements for you.
まず始めに、会場の皆様にご案内になります。
First, for those of you here at the venue.
本公演は声を出しての応援がOKになっております。
Vocal cheering is permitted during this performance.
ただし、周りの人の迷惑となるような
However, please refrain from shouting in a way
大声を出す行為だけはしないように、ご協力をお願いします。
that disturbs others. We appreciate your cooperation.
立ち上がっての応援も大歓迎です。
Cheering while standing is also very welcome.
ただし、モッシュ、ダイブ、ジャンプ等の
However, dangerous acts such as moshing, diving, jumping,
危険行為は禁止とさせていただきます。
and so on are strictly prohibited.
ペンライトも大きく振り回して、周りの人の視界を妨げたり、
Please be careful not to block others' view or hit them
ぶつかったりしないようにご注意ください。
when waving your penlights.
また、指定の席からのご移動はしないようにお願いします。
Also, please do not move from your assigned seat.
周囲のお客様に配慮した上で、
While being considerate of those around you,
思いっきり盛り上がっていきましょう！
let's get as hyped up as possible!
本公演は、避難誘導灯の消灯を行います。
During this show, the emergency exit lights will be turned off.
万が一、避難が必要になった場合には、
In the unlikely event that evacuation is necessary,
すぐに非常灯を点灯しますので、
we will immediately turn the emergency lights back on.
係員の指示に従っていただきますよう、よろしくお願いします。
Please follow the staff's instructions. Thank you.
公演終了後は規制退場を行います。
After the show, we will conduct a guided dispersal.
スタッフの指示があるまで自分の席で待っててね。
Please wait at your seat until instructed by staff.
また、このライブの中で気分が悪くなったり、
Also, if you feel unwell or if anything happens
何かあった場合には、早めに近くのスタッフさんに声をかけてください。
during the live, please inform a nearby staff member immediately.
場内での許可のない録音、撮影は禁止となっております。
Recording and photography without permission is prohibited in the venue.
そのような行為を見つけた場合は、ご退場いただく場合がございます。
If you are found doing so, you may be asked to leave.
携帯電話やスマートフォンは、音や振動を止めて、
Please silence your phones and smartphones,
見えないところにしまっておいてください。
and keep them out of sight.
本公演は、映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが場内に入るため、
Since there are cameras for streaming and photography inside,
お客様の様子が映り込んでしまう場合があります。
audience members may appear in the footage.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションや今後の活動に
These images and videos may be used for promotion
使用する可能性がダイダイダイ！になっておりますので、
and future activities, very very very likely!
あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware of this in advance.
嫌な人は顔を隠すんま！
If you don't like it, hide your face!
危険行為や禁止行為を見つけた場合、
If dangerous or prohibited acts are spotted,
スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございます。
staff members will give you a warning.
ルールを守っていただけない場合には、安全確保のため、
If rules are not followed, to ensure everyone's safety,
公演を一時中断、もしくは中止となる可能性もございます。
the show may be paused or even cancelled.
ルールをしっかり守って、みんなで楽しいライブにしましょう。
Let's all follow the rules and have a fun live together!
続いて、配信のみんなに注意事項をお伝えいたします。
Next, some announcements for those of you on the stream.
最善の準備を行いライブ配信を実施いたしますが、
We've prepared our best for this live broadcast,
生配信の特性上、不慮の障害で映像の乱れや
but due to the nature of live streaming, unexpected issues
一時停止等が起こる可能性がございます。あらかじめご了承ください。
like lag or pauses may occur. Please understand.
また、本ライブの録音、録画、ミラー配信や
Also, recording, re-streaming, or illegal uploads
違法アップロードは固くお断りしております。ダメです！
of this show are strictly forbidden. No-no!
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して
Instead, taking screenshots and posting them
画像とともにSNSにご投稿いただくことは大歓迎です！
to SNS with your comments is very welcome!
本公演のハッシュタグは、「#ねぽらぼT4U」です。
The hashtag for this show is #ねぽらぼT4U (#NepolaboT4U).
ぜひハッシュタグを使って、ライブを一緒に盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag to hype up the live with us!
以上が開演前のご案内となります。
That's all for the pre-show announcements.
ライブの開演までもうすぐです。今しばらくお待ちください。
The live will start soon. Please wait a bit longer.
一緒にライブ盛り上がっていこう！
Let's get hyped up together!
みんなでいっぱ盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's all have an amazing time! Let's go!
あー！
Aah!
おー！
Ooh!
もう少し待っててねー！
Wait just a little longer!
Yukihana Lamy
雪花ラミィ
Momosuzu Nene
桃鈴ねね
Shishiro Botan
獅白ぼたん
Omaru Polka
尾丸ポルカ
Twinkle 4 You
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn hearts resonate
最高な時間　最高な仲間と
The best time with the best friends
煌めきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
お待たせー！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ねね！
Nene!
はーい、行きまーす！
Okay, here I go!
覚えてるかな？最初の歌
Do you remember? Our first song
懐かしいね
It's nostalgic
私の声が震えていた
My voice was trembling
ごめん、少し
Sorry, just a little
あの日から続く未来は
The future that continues from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is today, which we seized with everyone
もっと　もっと　もっと　もっと
More, more, more, more
加速するハート
A heart that accelerates
一緒に行くよ　どこまでも
We'll go together, wherever
I'm ready　準備はOK？
I'm ready, are you ready?
開け夢の扉を
Open the door to dreams
煌めき　未来　（スター）
Sparkle, Future (Star)
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn hearts resonate
最高な時間　最高な仲間と
The best time with the best friends
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディ
A melody that never ends
煌めきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
Yeah!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
2曲目、もっともっと盛り上がっていこうー！
2nd song, let's get even more hyped up!
届いてるかな？私の声
Is it reaching you? My voice
はっきりと
Clearly
届けたいのは君に笑顔
What I want to deliver to you is a smile
そのスマイル
That smile
理想の動作に悔しくて
Regretting the ideal movements
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together with everyone
ぎゅっと　ぎゅっと　ぎゅっと　ぎゅっと
Tightly, tightly, tightly, tightly
全て抱きしめて
Embrace everything
一緒に行こう　どこまでも
Let's go together, wherever
I'm ready　準備はOK？
I'm ready, are you ready?
進め希望の道を
Move forward on the path of hope
煌めき　未来　（スター）
Sparkle, Future (Star)
好きな気持ち　カラフルに奏でたいな
I want to play my feelings of love colorfully
最高の場所　最高のみんなと
In the best place with the best people
ここにいるよ　幻なんかじゃない
I'm here, it's not a hallucination
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart is dyed with happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
Accumulating harmony
煌めき纏って
Wrapped in sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願い　わがままもいいでしょ？
Such a wish, a little selfishness is okay, right?
だって楽しすぎて止まらない
Because it's too much fun to stop
輝くステージでもっともっとずっと
On the shining stage, more and more, forever
みんなー！会いたかったぞー！！
Everyone! I've wanted to see you!!
ねねも！会いたかったよー！会いたかったよー！
Nene too! I've wanted to see you! I've wanted to see you!
嬉しい　楽しい　愛おしいだけじゃ語れない
Happy, fun, precious, I can't just describe it with those
今も今も悩みはあるけれど
Even now, even now, there are worries, but...
ここにいるよ　私　ここにいるよ
I'm here, I'm right here
君と同じ世界を
The same world as you
見つめて
Gazing at it
キラメキライター！
Twinkle Writer!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let the brand-new heartbeats resound
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best friends
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm here, because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんな歌おう！
Everyone, sing!
せーの！
Ready, go!
終わらないメロディ
The never-ending melody
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
キラメキまとって
Wearing the sparkle
イェーイ！
Yay!
みんなー！2曲目からも飛ばしていくぞー！
Everyone! We're gonna keep it going from the second song too!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
今日は楽しんでいってね！
Please enjoy today!
それっ　ずっと　どこまでも踏み出そう
That's it, let's step out forever, anywhere
銀河の真ん中　笑い合って
In the middle of the galaxy, laughing together
みんな！ペンライトもっともっと見せてー！
Everyone! Show your penlights more and more!
もっともっと見せてー！
Show them more and more!
一歩目が　すでに幾何学
The first step is already geometric
きらり　渦に巻き込まれた
Sparkling, I was swept into the vortex
違うよ　出会いたくて
No, I wanted to meet you
ほら　みんな　ここにいる
Look, everyone is here
夢じゃないようで　だけどね
It doesn't seem like a dream, but you know
ファンタジーじゃない予感
A premonition that it's not fantasy
流星群　負けないよ
Meteor shower, I won't lose
光　放って
Releasing the light
どんな憧れも　飛び越えて
Surpassing any yearning
銀河の真ん中　更新しよう
In the middle of the galaxy, let's update
キラメキの標にさ　足跡だって星になる
The footprints on the beacon of sparkle will also become stars
One Two Three Yeah! 弾き散りばめ
One Two Three Yeah! Scattering the sparks
One Two Three Yeah! 山彦伝播
One Two Three Yeah! Echoing propagation
One Two Three Yeah! 旅していく季節が
One Two Three Yeah! The season we travel through
今始まったんだよ　きっと
Has surely just begun
銀河の心臓はいつも
The heart of the galaxy is always
燃えてるんだ　恒星のよう
Burning, like a fixed star
だからね　手を繋いだら
So, if we hold hands
生まれるものがある
Something will be born
それは新しい宇宙
That is a new universe
君と描く場所
The place I draw with you
仲間集め　世界を作ろう
Gather friends, let's create a world
気づいてみたら　冒険の真っ只中　星の海を渡れ　スパークルで
When I realized it, I was in the middle of an adventure, cross the sea of stars with a sparkle
どこまでも踏み出そう
Let's step out forever
星雲をかき分けて
Pushing through the nebula
無限の空が待ってるよ
The infinite sky is waiting
準備OK？　逆らってけ！
Ready? Go against it!
輝きは止まらない
The sparkle won't stop
銀河の真ん中　新世界
In the middle of the galaxy, a new world
君となら行けるから　願いの向こう　未来へと
Since I can go if I'm with you, beyond the wish, to the future
One Two Three Yeah! 弾き散りばめ
One Two Three Yeah! Scattering the sparks
One Two Three Yeah! 山彦伝播
One Two Three Yeah! Echoing propagation
One Two Three Yeah! 旅していく季節が
One Two Three Yeah! The season we travel through
今始まったんだよ　きっと
Has surely just begun
Wonderful Zoo-a
はい、みなさーん！
Hi everyone!
こんねぽらぼー！
Kon-nepolabo!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ホロライブ5期生ライブ...
Hololive 5th Gen Live...
...Twinkle 4 You!
届いたかなー？
Did it reach you?
お待たせしましたー！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
5期生にとっての初めてのライブ、やっとできたね！
The first live for the 5th gen, we finally did it!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということで、自己紹介をしましょうか！
So, shall we do our self-introductions?
しましょー！やりましょー！
Let's do it! Let's go!
じゃあ、ねぽらぼのね、ね、ね、はい！
Then NePolabo's Ne, Ne, Ne, Hi!
みんな、オレンジのライトお願いしまーす！
Everyone, orange lights please!
めっちゃ綺麗！
So beautiful!
おー、すごーい！
Oh, amazing!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
じゃあ、ねねがみんなの心のーって聞いたら、
Then, when Nene asks "Everyone's heart's...",
みんなは「エナジードリンクー！」って叫んでね！
everyone shout "Energy Drink!"
エナジードリンクやでみんな！エナジー、エナジー！
Energy Drink everyone! Energy, energy!
エナジードリンクな！はい！
Energy drink! Okay!
いきますよー！ホロライブ5期生オレンジ担当、
Here we go! Hololive 5th gen orange representative,
みんなの心のー！
everyone's heart's...!
エナジードリンクー！
Energy Drink!
桃鈴ねねです！いえーい！
I'm Momosuzu Nene! Yay!
はーい、ポルだー！いくぜいくぜいくぜ！
Yes, it's Pol! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
ポルカ真ん中移動するぞー！はい！
Polka is moving to the center! Okay!
はーい！ポルカ、おるか、おるよ！ホロライブ5期生、尾丸ポルカです！
Yes! Polka, oruka, oruyo! Hololive 5th gen, I'm Omaru Polka!
え、待って、こんなライブですよ！
Wait, it's a live like this!
あららら... ライブやで！あららら...
Oh my... it's a live! Oh my...
攻略しちまったな！
We've cleared it!
ライブですけど、みんな、どうやら俺らに力を貸してくれっていう感じだ！
It's a live, but it seems like everyone is willing to lend us their strength!
どういう感じですか？なるほど。
What kind of feeling is that? I see.
まだ解放してなかった、ポルカの全ての力を。なので...
I haven't released all of Polka's power yet. So...
...みんな「ポルカおるか？」って聞いてくれるかな？
...everyone, can you ask "Polka's there?"
「せーの」って言うので、そしたら「ポルカおるかー！」って聞いてくれるかな？
I'll say "ready, go", then please ask "Polka's there?"
「ポルカおるかー！」って聞けばいいんですか？
Should we ask "Polka's there?"
ちょっとね、お勧めだけどね。
Well, I recommend it.
いくよ！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
ポルカおるかー！
Is Polka there?
はい！おんじゃ！ホロライブ5期生、尾丸ポルカでしたー！
Yes! There! Hololive 5th gen, it was Omaru Polka!
今日はよろしくー！
Let's have fun today!
いえーい！じゃあ次、ラミィかな！青色、青色！
Yay! Then next is Lamy! Blue, blue!
みんなー！みんなー！
Everyone! Everyone!
分かってるよね！？え、何？
You know, right!? Eh, what?
ラミィ、ラミィって言ったら、みんな何て言うのー？
When I say "Lamy, Lamy", what will you say?
あ、分かってる！すごいなー！
Ah, you know! Amazing!
じゃあ、「愛してるのはー？」って言ったら...
Then, when I say "The one I love is..."?
愛してるー！
I love you!
統率取れてる！すごーい！
They're so well-coordinated! Amazing!
ということで、改めまして。ラミィちゃんしかー！？
So, once again. Only Lamy-chan!?
愛してるー！
I love you!
愛してるのはー！？ラミィちゃーん！
The one I love is!? Lamy-chan!
ありがとうございます！ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです！
Thank you very much! I'm Yukihana Lamy of Hololive 5th gen!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
あらららら... 獅白さん来ちゃって。
Oh my... Shishiro-san is up.
獅白はいつも通りね、ちょっとシンプルにいきますんで。
Shishiro will go with something simple, as always.
はい、いきます。ラライオン！ホロライブ5期生、獅白ぼたんです！
Okay, here I go. Lalaion! I'm Shishiro Botan of Hololive 5th gen!
ラライオンー！
Lalaion!
白い、真っ白、真っ白！
White, pure white!
あ、すみません、それ私が作ったあいさつですね。
Ah, excuse me, that's a greeting I made.
いけなーい！
Oops!
まだ擦ってるの！？その話？
Are you still rubbing it in? That story?
もう3年間ずっと獅白の話してるんだ、ラライオンのこと言ってるの。
For 3 years, you've been talking about Shishiro, talking about Lalaion.
それ後でやってもらっていいですか？後でDMするね。
Can you do that later? I'll DM you later.
だってこんな人がいるのにさー！やることかー！3年間ずっと呼んだよなー！
But there are so many people here! Is this the place for that!? I've been calling you that for 3 years!
そんなことよりも、自己紹介も終わったところで...
Anyway, now that we've finished our introductions...
みんな！ライブといえばー？
Everyone! Speaking of lives...?
何？ヘビ？装備？ウェーブ！
What? Snake? Equipment? Wave!
ウェーブでーす！やりたいの！？
It's a wave! You want to do it!?
やりたいだろー！
You want to do it, right!
さあ、ねねさん、上手にお願いしますよ！
Well, Nene-san, please do it skillfully!
じゃあねねが、オレンジの皆さん！
Then Nene will... Orange people!
こちら側からいきます！
We'll start from this side!
ねねが走りすぎたら、こうやって上げて下げてね。
When Nene runs past, raise and lower like this.
楽しいよ！
It's fun!
いくよ！せーの！ねぽらぼ最高ー！
Here we go! Ready, go! NePolabo is the best!
おー、すごい！おー、すごい！
Oh, amazing! Wow!
はい、ちょっと帰ってきてくださーい！
Please come back for a bit!
あ、ちょっと戻ってきて！
Ah, come back!
あ、そうだ！うわー！
Ah, that's right! Whoa!
早いなー！
That's fast!
すごーい！ラミィもやる！？
Amazing! Lamy, you want to do it too!?
ラミィもやりたーい！高速で切り替えられる？青、青、青！
Lamy wants to do it too! Can you switch at high speed? Blue, blue, blue!
あ、でもみんな高速で切り替えてる！すごーい！
Ah, but everyone is switching at high speed! Amazing!
Lamy: これも…ありがとう。じゃ、次…
Lamy: Thank you for this, too. Now, next...
Botan: 「愛してる！」で通り過ぎるからね。
Botan: I'll pass by with "I love you!"
Lamy: はい！せーの！
Lamy: Okay! One, two!
Group: ししろんしか！愛してる！
Group: Only Shishiron! I love you!
Lamy: すごいゆっくり…！
Lamy: That was so slow!
Botan: 恥ずかしいよ！
Botan: This is embarrassing!
Botan: もっと早く！もっと早さを感じたい！
Botan: Faster! I want to feel more speed!
Group: 愛してる！愛してる！
Group: I love you! I love you!
Lamy: じゃ、私も！私も！
Lamy: Me too! Me too!
Nene: よし、しらみ（しらみ）やろう！全員やろう！
Nene: All right, let's do Shira-Mi! Everyone, let's go!
Botan: じゃ、普段やんないけど…私も「愛してる」やりたいな。
Botan: Well, I don't usually do it, but... I want to do "I love you" too.
Botan: 普段やんないも〜ん。
Botan: Because I don't usually do it.
Botan: ししろんしか！愛してる！
Botan: Only Shishiron! I love you!
Polka: おいおいおい！仕様で取ります！めっちゃ早く行くからね！
Polka: Hey hey hey! Let's do it like this! We're going super fast!
Group: ししろんしか！愛してる！
Group: Only Shishiron! I love you!
Lamy: そんなに早くないですよ！
Lamy: That wasn't that fast!
Botan: 早くなかった？
Botan: It wasn't fast?
Polka: もっといける？もっといける？もっといける？
Polka: Can we go more? Can we go more? Can we go more?
Botan: クラウチングスタート！
Botan: Crouching start!
Group: ししろんしか！愛してる！
Group: Only Shishiron! I love you!
Botan: ふ〜！お待たせしました！
Botan: Phew! Sorry for the wait!
Lamy: じゃあ、次は…ポルカ？
Lamy: Then next... Polka?
Botan: ポルカは何でやるの？
Botan: What will Polka do?
Polka: ポルカ、おるか？じゃなくて…
Polka: Is Polka here? No, wait...
Polka: ポルカは普通に「わー！」で行くから。
Polka: Polka will just go with "Waa!"
Polka: ポルカがね、ここで一番最後にお手本見せるってわけ。
Polka: Polka will show the example at the very end.
Lamy: 最後にお手本見せるって…
Lamy: Show the example at the end...
Polka: 皆さん、まずペンライト赤ありがとうございます！そちらは…
Polka: Everyone, first, thank you for the red penlights! Over there...
Polka: まず皆さん、お手元の腕を下ろしていただいてから始めましょうか。
Polka: First, everyone, please lower your arms before we start.
Polka: じゃ、ポルカこっち走り去って行くから…
Polka: Then, Polka will run away this way...
Polka: …そのポルカが来るタイミングで上げるんだよ！最後だよ！
Polka: ...and you raise them when Polka comes! This is the end!
Group: せーの！わー！
Group: One, two! Waa!
Polka: はい完璧！みんな拍手！
Polka: Yes, perfect! Everyone, applause!
Polka: 自分に拍手！隣の人にも拍手して！
Polka: Give yourselves a round of applause! And to the people next to you too!
Polka: イェーイ！パチパチパチ！はい完璧。
Polka: Yeah! *clap clap clap* Yes, perfect.
Polka: じゃあ、ちょっと何か…満足したよね。
Polka: Well, I'm kind of... satisfied now.
Botan: 満足してないけどね！
Botan: I'm not satisfied, though!
Lamy: みんな疲れただろうから…
Lamy: Everyone must be tired...
Polka: お水飲んでな！お水飲んで！
Polka: Drink some water! Drink some water!
Polka: まぁ、言うてもライブだからね、歌もほら歌わないとだな。
Polka: Well, it is a live concert, so we have to sing.
Nene: あ、そうだった！そうだった！すみません、すみません、忘れてました！
Nene: Ah, that's right! Sorry, sorry, I forgot!
Nene: 皆様にちょっとお知らせなんですけど…何ですか？
Nene: I have a bit of an announcement for everyone... What is it?
Nene: しらみ（しらみ）の方、次の曲までに…
Nene: For Shira-Mi, by the next song...
Nene: …「チラ見せ」は終わりなんです！
Nene: ...the "sneak peek" will be over!
Botan: 最後まで見たい人はどうしたらいいんだろう？
Botan: What should those who want to see until the end do?
Lamy: えーと、最後まで見たい方はですね、概要欄の方チェックしてください。
Lamy: Well, for those who want to see until the end, please check the description.
Polka: 配信に向けてのお知らせです。
Polka: That was an announcement for the stream.
Polka: 現地はどれだけ盛り上がってるか、大きな元気な声聞かせてくれるかな？
Polka: How hyped is the venue? Can I hear your loud, energetic voices?
Polka: どうだ？！イェーイ！
Polka: How is it?! Yeah!
Polka: さ、これを聞くとネットもほら盛り上がってる！
Polka: Hear that? The internet is hyped too!
Lamy: 盛り上がってる！捌ききれないほど盛り上がっておりますですが…
Lamy: It's hyped! It's so hyped we can't handle it, but...
Polka: …次の曲は、じゃあめっちゃ盛り上げていこうぜ、ねね！
Polka: ...for the next song, let's get super hyped, Nene!
Nene: 行こうぜ！パンパカパン…
Nene: Let's go! Ta-da!
Polka: 話聞いてなかったでしょ今。 Nene: ねね！はい！
Polka: You weren't listening, were you? Nene: Nene! Yes!
Polka: 感謝してる場合じゃねえです。あのね…
Polka: This is no time to be feeling thankful. Look...
Polka: …無料パート最後だから思いっきり盛り上げていきましょう！
Polka: ...it's the end of the free part, so let's get hyped to the max!
Polka: 最初は、ねね・ポルカメインで歌うから…
Polka: First, Nene and Polka will sing mainly...
Polka: …しらみがダンスで参加してもらいます！
Polka: ...and Shira-Mi will join in with dance!
Botan: お、じゃあねねちゃん行ってくれるかな？
Botan: Oh, then Nene-chan, will you lead us?
Nene: はい！それじゃあ早速次の曲、聞いてください。せーの！ Let's Go!
Nene: Yes! Well then, please listen to the next song. Ready? Let's Go!
Yeah! Ra-ra-ra-mi-ne... Botan... Polka! Oh yeah!
Let's Go Jumpin' Jumpin' Now! Da-da-da-ba-ra-ra-ra-pa!
Let's Go Jumpin' Jumpin' Jump!
Let's Go Jumpin' Jumpin' Ban!
子供だましのmathematica...
A child's trick of mathematica...
割れ電卓そんなんでプライドがない！
A broken calculator, no pride in that!
Clipping motion 一人で...
Clipping motion, all alone...
そこ見る見物分ばかりじゃつまんね！
Just watching from there is boring!
ほらぼっち、間違ってちょっと...
Hey, loner, make a little mistake...
退屈に手をかけて...
Laying hands on boredom...
Um-ma-ma! やっぱ私は...
Um-ma-ma! After all, I...
こんなところじゃ終われない！
Can't end in a place like this!
ムムでlook 気が触れた...
Look with a frown, gone mad...
ごっこ遊びも芝居もさよなら！
Goodbye to make-believe and acting!
ずっとこのままなんてさ！
Staying like this forever is...
色んなようだった…私大人になる！
I was many things... I'm becoming an adult!
酸いも甘いも噛み締めて今...
Tasting both the bitter and the sweet now...
Ba-ba-ba 変わる時代...
Ba-ba-ba, changing times...
悪いことばかりじゃないでしょ？
It's not all bad things, right?
どこまでも、今も、集め...
Everywhere, even now, gather...
全て、全て、愛して...
Love everything, everything...
生きてやり返すわ！ Yeah!
I'll live and get back at them! Yeah!
挑発 私たちはのdance!
Provocation, our dance!
緑のあいつにばっかかまってね...
Don't just pay attention to that green guy...
像パンダ道なったらもらえる合格！
If I become like an elephant, I'll pass!
赤さえ入れておけばダメなんですか？
Is it no good if I just add red?
酒お待たせら…やっちゃって…！
Wait for the sake... just do it...!
冗談じゃない！
I'm not kidding!
泣き止んだら強くなるような...
Like getting stronger after you stop crying...
ママ　なんか要らない
Mom, I don't need anything
欲しがります勝つまでは
I'll keep wanting it until I win
伸びたった丈　それだけだった...
The height I've grown, that was all...
街に投げキッス見せたったわ　これから
I gave a blowing kiss to my town, from now on
覚悟しとけよ
Get ready for this!
ダッダッダッダ　僕ら大人になる
Da-da-da-da, we're becoming adults
カウンター狙え　最低な日々に
Aim for a counter-attack on these worst days
淡々とカマしていけ
Keep pushing through coolly
誰も止めれない先へと
To a place where no one can stop us
如何でしょう？（着替え！）
How's this? (Change clothes!)
任せ！（くれなえ！）
Leave it to me! (Give it to me!)
全て！（捨てて！）
Everything! (Throw it away!)
生き抜いて！（生き抜いて！）
Survive! (Survive!)
覆すよ
I'll overturn it all
ダッダッダ　下らない事ばっか譲れない
Da-da-da, I won't give in on trivial things
解るか　あたしの美学
Do you understand my aesthetic?
この馬鹿正直な
This honest-to-a-fault...
拳一つが
A single fist
一途なんです
Is single-minded
切り札
Trump card
ああ　愚直なんです
Ah, it's simple-minded
奏でるわ
The performance...
一撃KOさ
Is a one-hit KO!
さらば！
Farewell!
Oh oh oh...
今夜も止まらない
It won't stop tonight either
ダッダッダッダ　あたし大人になる
Da-da-da-da, I'm becoming an adult
酸いも甘いも噛み分けていな
Experiencing both the bitter and the sweet
散々交わり未来も
Mixing it up thoroughly, even the future
お固まりじゃないの　解るでしょう？
It's not set in stone, can't you tell?
着替え！　任せ！
Change! Leave it!
紅！　全て！
Deep red! Everything!
捨てて！　生き抜いて！
Throw it away! Survive!
ちょっとだわ
It's just a bit
アイヤイの時間！
It's Aiyai time!
それでは皆様お先にバイバーイ！
Well then everyone, we'll head out first. Bye-bye!
フロアが沸き上がりました！
The floor is heating up!
無料パートは終了いたしました
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free portion of the stream has ended.
Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Thank you for watching
はい、ということで...
Yes, so...
ニコニコ動画での無料チラ見せパートは
the free preview part on Niconico Douga
ここまでとなります。
is over as of now.
ここからは Z-aN、ニコニコ動画それぞれの
From here on, for Z-aN and Niconico Douga respectively,
チケットをお持ちの方のみの
it will be a broadcast
放送となります！
only for those with tickets!
ぜひ最後まで楽しんでいってください！
Please enjoy yourselves until the end!
それでは、引き続き
Well then, please continue
Twinkle 4 You をお楽しみください！
to enjoy Twinkle 4 You!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!